{
  "accent": "",
  "front": "de",
  "name": "Duolingo German",
  "cards": [
    {
      "back": "man",
      "front": "Mann",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "woman",
      "front": "Frau",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "boy",
      "front": "Junge",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "girl",
      "front": "Mädchen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to be",
      "front": "sein",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "a",
      "front": "ein",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "the",
      "front": "der/die/das",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "I",
      "front": "ich",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "you",
      "front": "du",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "he",
      "front": "er",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "she",
      "front": "sie (f)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "it",
      "front": "es",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to eat",
      "front": "essen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to drink",
      "front": "trinken",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "apple",
      "front": "Apfel",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "bread",
      "front": "Brot",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "water",
      "front": "Wasser",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "we",
      "front": "wir",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "you",
      "front": "ihr",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "they",
      "front": "sie (pl)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "newspaper",
      "front": "Zeitung",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "milk",
      "front": "Milch",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "sandwich",
      "front": "Sandwich",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "rice",
      "front": "Reis",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "child",
      "front": "Kind",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "children",
      "front": "Kinder",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "book",
      "front": "Buch",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "menu",
      "front": "Speisekarte",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to have",
      "front": "haben",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Hello!",
      "front": "Hallo!",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Bye! / Goodbye!",
      "front": "Tschüss!",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "thanks",
      "front": "danke",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "yes",
      "front": "ja",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "no",
      "front": "nein",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "please",
      "front": "bitte",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "How are you?",
      "front": "Wie geht es dir?",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "I’m fine.",
      "front": "Mir geht es gut.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Good morning!",
      "front": "Guten Morgen!",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Good night!",
      "front": "Gute Nacht",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Welcome!",
      "front": "Willkommen!",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Sorry! / Excuse me!",
      "front": "entschuldigung",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "not",
      "front": "nicht",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to speak / to talk",
      "front": "sprechen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "English",
      "front": "Englisch",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Do you speak English?",
      "front": "Sprechen Sie Englisch?",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "fish",
      "front": "Fisch",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "orange",
      "front": "Orange",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "wine",
      "front": "Wein",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "coffee",
      "front": "Kaffee",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "egg",
      "front": "Ei",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "chicken",
      "front": "Hähnchen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "plate",
      "front": "Teller",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "sugar",
      "front": "Zucker",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "lunch",
      "front": "Mittagessen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "breakfast",
      "front": "Frühstück",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "dinner",
      "front": "Abendessen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "cheese",
      "front": "Käse",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "fruit",
      "front": "Frucht",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "pasta",
      "front": "Nudeln",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "juice",
      "front": "Saft",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "beer",
      "front": "Bier",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "beef",
      "front": "Rindfleisch",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "soup",
      "front": "Suppe",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "tomato",
      "front": "Tomate",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "strawberry",
      "front": "Erdbeere",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "lemon",
      "front": "Zitrone",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "food",
      "front": "Essen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "oil",
      "front": "Öl",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "salt",
      "front": "Salz",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "meat",
      "front": "Fleisch",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "meal",
      "front": "Mahlzeit",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "tea",
      "front": "Tee",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "pork",
      "front": "Schweinefleisch",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "vegetarian",
      "front": "vegetarisch",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "cat",
      "front": "Katze",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "dog",
      "front": "Hund",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "horse",
      "front": "Pferd",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "bird",
      "front": "Vogel",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "elephant",
      "front": "Elefant",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "duck",
      "front": "Ente",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "turtle",
      "front": "Schildkröte",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "crab",
      "front": "Krabbe",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "spider",
      "front": "Spinne",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "animal",
      "front": "Tier",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "bear",
      "front": "Bär",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "mouse",
      "front": "Maus",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "my",
      "front": "mein",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "your",
      "front": "dein",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "his",
      "front": "sein (m)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "her",
      "front": "ihr (f)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "its",
      "front": "sein (n)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "our",
      "front": "unser",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "your",
      "front": "euer",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "their",
      "front": "ihr (pl)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "It’s mine.",
      "front": "Es ist mir.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "It’s yours.",
      "front": "Es ist dir.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "It’s ours.",
      "front": "Es ist uns.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "It’s theirs.",
      "front": "Es ist ihnen.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "me",
      "front": "mir/mich",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "you",
      "front": "dir/dich",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "him",
      "front": "ihm/ihn",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "her",
      "front": "ihr/sie",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "it",
      "front": "ihm/es",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "us",
      "front": "uns",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "you",
      "front": "euch",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "them",
      "front": "ihnen/sie",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "you",
      "front": "Ihnen/Sie",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to wear",
      "front": "tragen (Kleidung)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "shirt",
      "front": "Hemd",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "shoe",
      "front": "Schuh",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "skirt",
      "front": "Rock",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "coat",
      "front": "Mantel",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "dress",
      "front": "Kleid",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "pants",
      "front": "Hose",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "clothes",
      "front": "Kleidung",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "suit",
      "front": "Anzug",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "hat",
      "front": "Hut",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to write",
      "front": "schreiben",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to do",
      "front": "tun",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to walk",
      "front": "laufen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to swim",
      "front": "schwimmen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to see",
      "front": "sehen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to cook",
      "front": "kochen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to sleep",
      "front": "schlafen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to run",
      "front": "rennen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to want",
      "front": "wollen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to like",
      "front": "mögen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to pay",
      "front": "bezahlen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to go",
      "front": "gehen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to play",
      "front": "spielen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to use",
      "front": "benutzen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to love",
      "front": "lieben",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "it rains",
      "front": "es regnet",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to touch",
      "front": "berühren",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to hear",
      "front": "hören",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to listen",
      "front": "zuhören",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to say",
      "front": "sagen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to tell",
      "front": "erzählen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to make",
      "front": "machen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to find",
      "front": "finden",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to work",
      "front": "arbeiten",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to support",
      "front": "unterstützen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to know",
      "front": "wissen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to need",
      "front": "brauchen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to take",
      "front": "nehmen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to design",
      "front": "gestalten",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to show",
      "front": "zeigen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "red",
      "front": "rot",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "orange",
      "front": "orange",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "white",
      "front": "weiß",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "black",
      "front": "schwarz",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "blue",
      "front": "blau",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "yellow",
      "front": "gelb",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "green",
      "front": "grün",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "gray",
      "front": "grau",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "brown",
      "front": "braun",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "pink",
      "front": "pink",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "purple",
      "front": "lila",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "color",
      "front": "Farbe",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "colorful",
      "front": "farbig",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "What?",
      "front": "Was?",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Where?",
      "front": "Wo?",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "How?",
      "front": "Wie?",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Who?",
      "front": "Wer?",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Why?",
      "front": "Warum",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Whose?",
      "front": "Wessen?",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Which?",
      "front": "Welches?",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "When?",
      "front": "Wann?",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "question",
      "front": "Frage",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "answer",
      "front": "Antwort",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "and",
      "front": "und",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "or",
      "front": "oder",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "but",
      "front": "aber",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "if",
      "front": "wenn (falls)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "because",
      "front": "weil",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "when",
      "front": "wenn (sobald)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "whenever",
      "front": "immer wenn",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "that",
      "front": "dass",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "from Germany",
      "front": "aus Deutschland",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "in",
      "front": "in",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "on",
      "front": "auf",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "at",
      "front": "an",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "of",
      "front": "von",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "between",
      "front": "zwischen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "by me",
      "front": "von mir",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "for",
      "front": "für",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "a book about …",
      "front": "ein Buch über …",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "with",
      "front": "mit",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "without",
      "front": "ohne",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to",
      "front": "zu",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "like for example",
      "front": "wie zum Beispiel",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "the same as",
      "front": "dasselbe wie",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "after",
      "front": "nach",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "out",
      "front": "heraus",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "under",
      "front": "unter",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to turn off",
      "front": "ausschalten",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "during",
      "front": "während",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "among them",
      "front": "unter ihnen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "behind",
      "front": "hinter",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "towards",
      "front": "zu … hin",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "near",
      "front": "nahe bei",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "over",
      "front": "über",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "except",
      "front": "außer",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "against",
      "front": "gegen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "today",
      "front": "heute",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "tomorrow",
      "front": "morgen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "tonight",
      "front": "heute Abend",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "night",
      "front": "Nacht",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "morning",
      "front": "Morgen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "afternoon",
      "front": "Nachmittag",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "evening",
      "front": "Abend",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "time",
      "front": "Zeit",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "calendar",
      "front": "Kalender",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Monday",
      "front": "Montag",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Tuesday",
      "front": "Dienstag",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Wednesday",
      "front": "Mittwoch",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Thursday",
      "front": "Donnerstag",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Friday",
      "front": "Freitag",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Saturday",
      "front": "Samstag",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Sunday",
      "front": "Sonntag",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "year",
      "front": "Jahr",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "age",
      "front": "Alter",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "week",
      "front": "Woche",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "month",
      "front": "Monat",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "hour",
      "front": "Stunde",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "January",
      "front": "Januar",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "February",
      "front": "Februar",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "March",
      "front": "März",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "April",
      "front": "April",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "May",
      "front": "Mai",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "June",
      "front": "Juni",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "July",
      "front": "Juli",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "August",
      "front": "August",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "September",
      "front": "September",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "October",
      "front": "Oktober",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "November",
      "front": "November",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "December",
      "front": "Dezember",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "date",
      "front": "Datum",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "season",
      "front": "Jahreszeit",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "winter",
      "front": "Winter",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "spring",
      "front": "Frühling",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "summer",
      "front": "Sommer",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "fall / autumn",
      "front": "Herbst",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "period",
      "front": "Zeitspanne",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "minute",
      "front": "Minute",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "century",
      "front": "Jahrhundert",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "party",
      "front": "Feier",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "stage",
      "front": "Bühne",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "generation",
      "front": "Generation",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "birth",
      "front": "Geburt",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "moment",
      "front": "Moment",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "fair",
      "front": "Messe, Jahrmarkt",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "decade",
      "front": "Jahrzehnt",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "second",
      "front": "Sekunde",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "a little / a bit",
      "front": "ein bisschen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "until",
      "front": "bis",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "mother",
      "front": "Mutter",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "father",
      "front": "Vater",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "parents",
      "front": "Eltern",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "son",
      "front": "Sohn",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "daughter",
      "front": "Tochter",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "brother",
      "front": "Bruder",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "sister",
      "front": "Schwester",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "siblings",
      "front": "Geschwister",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "husband",
      "front": "Ehemann",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "wife",
      "front": "Ehefrau",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "uncle",
      "front": "Onkel",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "aunt",
      "front": "Tante",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "family",
      "front": "Familie",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "marriage",
      "front": "Ehe",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "wedding",
      "front": "Hochzeit",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "mom",
      "front": "Mama",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "dad",
      "front": "Papa",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "grandmother / grandma",
      "front": "Großmutter",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "grandfather / grandpa",
      "front": "Großvater",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "name",
      "front": "Name",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "pupil",
      "front": "Schüler",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "student",
      "front": "Student",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "doctor",
      "front": "Doktor",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "work",
      "front": "Arbeit",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "author",
      "front": "Autor",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "job",
      "front": "Job",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "model",
      "front": "Model",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "staff",
      "front": "Personal",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "director",
      "front": "Direktor",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "director",
      "front": "Regisseur",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "career",
      "front": "Karriere",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "police",
      "front": "Polizei",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "policeman",
      "front": "Polizist",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "artist",
      "front": "Künstler",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "secretary",
      "front": "Sekretärin",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "worker",
      "front": "Arbeiter",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "lawyer",
      "front": "Anwalt",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "professional",
      "front": "professionell",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "judge",
      "front": "Richter",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "writer",
      "front": "Schriftsteller",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "officer",
      "front": "Beamter",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "guard",
      "front": "Wache",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "actor",
      "front": "Schauspieler",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "actress",
      "front": "Schauspielerin",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "captain",
      "front": "Kapitän",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "soldier",
      "front": "Soldat",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "boss",
      "front": "Chef",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "profession / occupation",
      "front": "Beruf",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "farmer",
      "front": "Bauer",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "architect",
      "front": "Architekt",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "waiter",
      "front": "Kellner",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "waitress",
      "front": "Kellnerin",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "cook",
      "front": "Koch",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "tired",
      "front": "müde",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "bilingual",
      "front": "zweisprachig",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "the same",
      "front": "dasselbe",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "next",
      "front": "nächste",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "general",
      "front": "generell",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "real",
      "front": "echt, wirklich (Adj.)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "local",
      "front": "lokal",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "special",
      "front": "speziell",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "previous",
      "front": "vorherig",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "open",
      "front": "offen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "my own car",
      "front": "mein eigenes Auto",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "personal",
      "front": "persönlich",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "main",
      "front": "Haupt-",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "private",
      "front": "privat",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "clean",
      "front": "sauber",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "dirty",
      "front": "dreckig",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "different",
      "front": "anders",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "left",
      "front": "links",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "right",
      "front": "rechts",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "human",
      "front": "menschlich",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "the recent",
      "front": "das letzte / neueste",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "legal",
      "front": "Rechts-",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "important",
      "front": "wichtig",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "available",
      "front": "verfügbar",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "future",
      "front": "zukünftig",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "possible",
      "front": "möglich",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "popular",
      "front": "beliebt",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "well-known",
      "front": "bekannt",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "official",
      "front": "offiziell",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "final",
      "front": "endgültig",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "whole",
      "front": "ganz",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "necessary",
      "front": "nötig",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "military",
      "front": "militärisch",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "independent",
      "front": "unanhängig",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "responsible",
      "front": "verantwortlich",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "excellent",
      "front": "vorzüglich",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "perfect",
      "front": "perfekt",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "beautiful",
      "front": "wunderbar, hübsch",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "modern",
      "front": "modern",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "positive",
      "front": "positiv",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "normal",
      "front": "normal",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "minimum",
      "front": "minimal",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "maximum",
      "front": "maximal",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "traditional",
      "front": "traditionell",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "wrong",
      "front": "falsch",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "historical",
      "front": "historisch",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "cultural",
      "front": "kulturell",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "interesting",
      "front": "interessant",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "religious",
      "front": "religiös",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "serious",
      "front": "ernst",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "famous",
      "front": "berühmt",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "negative",
      "front": "negativ",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "efficient",
      "front": "effizient",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "effective",
      "front": "effektiv",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "expensive",
      "front": "teuer",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to be familiar with sth.",
      "front": "vertraut sein mit etw.",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "impossible",
      "front": "unmöglich",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "alive",
      "front": "lebendig",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "convenient",
      "front": "geeignet / praktisch",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "opposite",
      "front": "Gegenteil",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to be afraid of",
      "front": "Angst haben vor",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "sad",
      "front": "traurig",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "frequent",
      "front": "häufig",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "wooden",
      "front": "aus Holz",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "golden",
      "front": "aus Gold",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to sign",
      "front": "unterschreiben",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to open",
      "front": "öffnen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to think",
      "front": "denken",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to change",
      "front": "ändern",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to return",
      "front": "umdrehen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to call",
      "front": "(an)rufen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to save",
      "front": "retten",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to save a file",
      "front": "eine Datei speichern",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to look",
      "front": "schauen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to look",
      "front": "aussehen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to live",
      "front": "leben",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to come",
      "front": "kommen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to study",
      "front": "studieren",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to offer",
      "front": "anbieten",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to give",
      "front": "geben",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to try",
      "front": "versuchen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to include",
      "front": "beinhalten",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to ask",
      "front": "fragen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to present",
      "front": "präsentieren",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to mark",
      "front": "markieren",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to feel",
      "front": "fühlen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to remember",
      "front": "sich erinnern",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to stop",
      "front": "anhalten",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to stop doing sth.",
      "front": "mit etwas aufhören",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to wish",
      "front": "wünschen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to hope",
      "front": "hoffen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to search / to look for",
      "front": "suchen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to fail",
      "front": "versagen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to fail an exam",
      "front": "durch eine Prüfung durchfallen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to pass an exam",
      "front": "eine Prüfung bestehen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to raise",
      "front": "erhöhen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to believe",
      "front": "glauben",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to follow",
      "front": "folgen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to thank",
      "front": "danken",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to consider",
      "front": "berücksichtigen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to seem",
      "front": "scheinen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to rest",
      "front": "ruhen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to answer / to respond",
      "front": "antworten",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to trust",
      "front": "vertrauen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to end",
      "front": "enden",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to start / to begin",
      "front": "anfangen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "there",
      "front": "dort",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "very",
      "front": "sehr",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "too / also",
      "front": "auch",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "now",
      "front": "jetzt",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "more",
      "front": "mehr",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "so",
      "front": "so",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "as",
      "front": "wie",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "never",
      "front": "nie",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "then",
      "front": "dann",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "here",
      "front": "hier",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "quite / fairly",
      "front": "ziemlich",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "always",
      "front": "immer",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "once",
      "front": "einmal",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "only / just",
      "front": "nur",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "well",
      "front": "gut (Adv.)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "even",
      "front": "sogar",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "still",
      "front": "immer noch",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "however",
      "front": "allerdings",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "really",
      "front": "wirklich (Adv.)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "again",
      "front": "wieder",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "not yet",
      "front": "noch nicht",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "away",
      "front": "weg",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "already",
      "front": "schon",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "at least",
      "front": "wenigstens",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ever",
      "front": "jemals",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "else",
      "front": "ansonsten",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "usually / normally",
      "front": "normalerweise",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "far away",
      "front": "weit weg",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "currently",
      "front": "im Moment",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "later",
      "front": "später",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "enough",
      "front": "genug",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "soon",
      "front": "bald",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "almost",
      "front": "fast",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "late",
      "front": "spät",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "especially",
      "front": "besonders",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "finally",
      "front": "endlich",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "sometimes",
      "front": "manchmal",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "completely",
      "front": "komplett",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "approximately",
      "front": "ungefähr",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "anywhere",
      "front": "irgendwo",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "twice",
      "front": "zweimal",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "neither … nor",
      "front": "weder … noch",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "either … or",
      "front": "entweder … oder",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "not necessarily",
      "front": "nicht unbedingt",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "definitely",
      "front": "definitiv",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "together",
      "front": "zusammen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "house",
      "front": "Haus",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "restaurant",
      "front": "Restaurant",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "beach",
      "front": "Strand",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "hotel",
      "front": "Hotel",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "yard",
      "front": "Hof",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "bathroom",
      "front": "Badezimmer",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "kitchen",
      "front": "Küche",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "airport",
      "front": "Flughafen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "street",
      "front": "Straße",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "city",
      "front": "Stadt (groß)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "church",
      "front": "Kirche",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "castle",
      "front": "Burg",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "country",
      "front": "Land",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "place",
      "front": "Ort",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "along",
      "front": "entlang",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "home",
      "front": "nach Hause",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "site",
      "front": "Standort",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "center",
      "front": "Zentrum",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "office",
      "front": "Büro",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "area / district",
      "front": "Gebiet",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "address",
      "front": "Adresse",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "department",
      "front": "Abteilung",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "property",
      "front": "Eigentum",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "room / space",
      "front": "Raum",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "market",
      "front": "Markt",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "park",
      "front": "Park",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "garden",
      "front": "Garten",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "region",
      "front": "Region",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "island",
      "front": "Insel",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "in front of",
      "front": "vor",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "bank",
      "front": "Bank (Geld)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "bench",
      "front": "Bank (sitzen)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "bar",
      "front": "Bar",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "inside",
      "front": "innen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "stadium",
      "front": "Stadion",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ground / soil",
      "front": "Grund, Boden",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "valley",
      "front": "Tal",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "museum",
      "front": "Museum",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "coast",
      "front": "Küste",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "zone",
      "front": "Zone",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "corner",
      "front": "Ecke",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "avenue / alley",
      "front": "Allee",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "route",
      "front": "Route",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "neighborhood",
      "front": "Nachbarschaft",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "border",
      "front": "Grenze (geogr.)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "tower",
      "front": "Turm",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "prison",
      "front": "Gefängnis",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "palace",
      "front": "Palast",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "town",
      "front": "Stadt",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "capital",
      "front": "Hauptstadt",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "community",
      "front": "Gemeinschaft",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "port",
      "front": "Hafen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "square",
      "front": "Platz (Stadt)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "at the top",
      "front": "oben",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "at the bottom",
      "front": "unten",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "west",
      "front": "Westen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "east",
      "front": "Osten",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "north",
      "front": "Norden",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "south",
      "front": "Süden",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "zoo",
      "front": "Zoo",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "farm",
      "front": "Bauernhof",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "building",
      "front": "Gebäude",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "cinema",
      "front": "Kino",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "table",
      "front": "Tisch",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "bed",
      "front": "Bett",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "chair",
      "front": "Stuhl",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "bowl",
      "front": "Schüssel",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "spoon",
      "front": "Löffel",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "bottle",
      "front": "Flasche",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "magazine",
      "front": "Zeitschrift",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "window",
      "front": "Fenster",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "television / TV",
      "front": "Fernseher",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "computer",
      "front": "Computer",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "radio",
      "front": "Radio",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "mirror",
      "front": "Spiegel",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "clock",
      "front": "Uhr",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "mobile phone / cellphone",
      "front": "Handy",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "watch",
      "front": "Armbanduhr",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "sofa",
      "front": "Sofa",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "lamp",
      "front": "Lampe",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "desk",
      "front": "Schreibtisch",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "basket",
      "front": "Korb",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "battery",
      "front": "Batterie",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "soap",
      "front": "Seife",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "bed sheet",
      "front": "Bettlaken",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "bedding",
      "front": "Bettwäsche",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "wallet / purse",
      "front": "Portmonee",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "door",
      "front": "Tür",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "box",
      "front": "Kiste",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "screen",
      "front": "Bildschirm",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "razor",
      "front": "Rasierapparat",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "toothpaste",
      "front": "Zahnpasta",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "telephone / phone",
      "front": "Telefon",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "wall",
      "front": "Wand",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "floor",
      "front": "Fußboden",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "bag",
      "front": "Tasche",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "wheel",
      "front": "Rad",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "umbrella",
      "front": "Schirm",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "roof",
      "front": "Dach",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "cupboard / cabinet",
      "front": "Schrank",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "letter",
      "front": "Brief",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "key",
      "front": "Schlüssel",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "pool",
      "front": "Schwimmbad",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "sponge",
      "front": "Schwamm",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "thing",
      "front": "Ding",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "bell",
      "front": "Glocke",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "scissors",
      "front": "Schere",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "glass",
      "front": "Glas",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "cup",
      "front": "Tasse",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "pan",
      "front": "Pfanne",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "paper",
      "front": "Papier",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "engine / motor",
      "front": "Motor",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "object",
      "front": "Objekt",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "machine",
      "front": "Maschine",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "string",
      "front": "Schnur",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "piece",
      "front": "Stück",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "a piece/sheet of paper",
      "front": "ein Blatt Papier",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "root",
      "front": "Wurzel",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "chain",
      "front": "Kette",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "flag",
      "front": "Fahne",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "novel",
      "front": "Roman",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "powder",
      "front": "Puder",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "comb",
      "front": "Kamm",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "through",
      "front": "durch",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "fork",
      "front": "Gabel",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "knife",
      "front": "Messer",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "toothbrush",
      "front": "Zahnbürste",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "person",
      "front": "Person",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "baby",
      "front": "Baby",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "friend",
      "front": "Freund(in)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "boyfriend",
      "front": "fester Freund",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "girlfriend",
      "front": "feste Freundin",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "public",
      "front": "öffentlich",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "enemy",
      "front": "Feind",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "committee",
      "front": "Ausschuss",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "conference",
      "front": "Konferenz",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "culture",
      "front": "Kultur",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "foundation",
      "front": "Stiftung",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "relationship",
      "front": "Beziehung",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "village",
      "front": "Dorf",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "individual",
      "front": "individuell",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "couple",
      "front": "Paar",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "a pair of shoes",
      "front": "ein Paar Schuhe",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "some / a few / a couple of",
      "front": "ein paar",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "lady",
      "front": "Dame",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "gentleman",
      "front": "Herr",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ladies and gentlemen",
      "front": "meine Damen und Herren",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "citizen",
      "front": "Bürger",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "victim",
      "front": "Opfer",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "people",
      "front": "Menschen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "youth",
      "front": "Jugend",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "the travelling",
      "front": "das Reisen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to travel",
      "front": "reisen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "car",
      "front": "Auto",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "bicycle / bike",
      "front": "Fahrrad",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "suitcase",
      "front": "Koffer",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "bus",
      "front": "Bus",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "train",
      "front": "Zug",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "motorcycle",
      "front": "Motorrad",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "boat",
      "front": "Boot",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "airplane / plane",
      "front": "Flugzeug",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to drive",
      "front": "fahren (Auto)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "backpack",
      "front": "Rucksack",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "guide",
      "front": "Reiseführer",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "visit",
      "front": "Besuch",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Spanish",
      "front": "Spanisch",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Portuguese",
      "front": "Portugiesisch",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "map",
      "front": "Karte",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "road",
      "front": "Landstraße",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ship",
      "front": "Schiff",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "vehicle",
      "front": "Fahrzeug",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "transport / transportation",
      "front": "Transport",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "trip",
      "front": "Ausflug",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Italian",
      "front": "Italienisch",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "French",
      "front": "Französisch",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "flight",
      "front": "Flug",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "adventure",
      "front": "Abenteuer",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "bridge",
      "front": "Brücke",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "journey",
      "front": "Reise",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "German",
      "front": "Deutsch",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "departure",
      "front": "Abreise",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "tourist",
      "front": "Tourist",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "subway",
      "front": "U-Bahn",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "America",
      "front": "Amerika",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "France",
      "front": "Frankreich",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Germany",
      "front": "Deutschland",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "England",
      "front": "England",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "United Kingdom",
      "front": "Vereinigtes Königreich",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Great Britain",
      "front": "Großbritannien",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Europe",
      "front": "Europa",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "China",
      "front": "China",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "abroad",
      "front": "im Ausland",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Chinese",
      "front": "Chinesisch",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "international",
      "front": "international",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "American",
      "front": "amerikanisch",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "European",
      "front": "europäisch",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "around the world",
      "front": "um die Welt",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to turn",
      "front": "drehen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "passport",
      "front": "Reisepass",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "this / these",
      "front": "diese(r) hier",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "that / those",
      "front": "diese(r) dort",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "one / you",
      "front": "man",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "all",
      "front": "alle",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "everybody / everyone",
      "front": "jeder",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "every day / each day",
      "front": "jeden Tag",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "some / any",
      "front": "irgendein",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "the other one",
      "front": "der andere",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "another one",
      "front": "ein anderer",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "something",
      "front": "etwas",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "such",
      "front": "solche",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "both",
      "front": "beide",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "few",
      "front": "wenig",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "everything",
      "front": "alles",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "none of this",
      "front": "nichts davon",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "somebody / someone",
      "front": "jemand",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "nothing",
      "front": "nichts",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "anything",
      "front": "irgendetwas",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "nobody / no one",
      "front": "niemand",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "anybody / anyone",
      "front": "irgendjemand",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "one",
      "front": "1",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "two",
      "front": "2",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "three",
      "front": "3",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "four",
      "front": "4",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "five",
      "front": "5",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "six",
      "front": "6",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "seven",
      "front": "7",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "eight",
      "front": "8",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "nine",
      "front": "9",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ten",
      "front": "10",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "eleven",
      "front": "11",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "twelve",
      "front": "12",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "thirteen",
      "front": "13",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "fourteen",
      "front": "14",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "fifteen",
      "front": "15",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "sixteen",
      "front": "16",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "seventeen",
      "front": "17",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "eighteen",
      "front": "18",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "nineteen",
      "front": "19",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "twenty",
      "front": "20",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "twenty-one",
      "front": "21",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "thirty",
      "front": "30",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "forty",
      "front": "40",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "fifty",
      "front": "50",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "sixty",
      "front": "60",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "seventy",
      "front": "70",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "eighty",
      "front": "80",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ninety",
      "front": "90",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "one hundred",
      "front": "100",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "one thousand",
      "front": "1000",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "thousands",
      "front": "tausende",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "one million",
      "front": "1000000",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "millions of people",
      "front": "Millionen Menschen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "first",
      "front": "erste",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "second",
      "front": "zweite",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "third",
      "front": "dritte",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "forth",
      "front": "vierte",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "fifth",
      "front": "fünfte",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "sixth",
      "front": "sechste",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "seventh",
      "front": "siebte",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "eighth",
      "front": "achte",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ninth",
      "front": "neunte",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "tenth",
      "front": "zehnte",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "some",
      "front": "manche",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "less",
      "front": "weniger",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "many / much / a lot of",
      "front": "viel",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "last",
      "front": "letzte",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "number",
      "front": "Zahl",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "amount of",
      "front": "Menge an",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "sum",
      "front": "Summe",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "majority",
      "front": "Mehrheit",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "minority",
      "front": "Minderheit",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "meter",
      "front": "Meter",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "average",
      "front": "Durchschnitt",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "half",
      "front": "Hälfte",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "kilometers per hour",
      "front": "km/h",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to contain",
      "front": "enthalten",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to get / to receive",
      "front": "erhalten, bekommen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to respect",
      "front": "respektieren",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to agree",
      "front": "zustimmen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to appear",
      "front": "erscheinen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to watch",
      "front": "beobachten",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to count",
      "front": "zählen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to miss",
      "front": "verpassen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to fill",
      "front": "füllen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to produce",
      "front": "herstellen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to reserve",
      "front": "reservieren",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to mix",
      "front": "mischen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to dry",
      "front": "trocknen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to fly",
      "front": "fliegen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to import",
      "front": "importieren",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to export",
      "front": "exportieren",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to help",
      "front": "helfen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to spend time",
      "front": "Zeit verbringen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to continue",
      "front": "weitermachen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to deliver",
      "front": "liefern",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to leave",
      "front": "verlassen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to hate",
      "front": "hassen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to assume",
      "front": "annehmen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to serve as",
      "front": "dienen als",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to create",
      "front": "erstellen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to add",
      "front": "hinzufügen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to visit",
      "front": "besuchen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to introduce",
      "front": "einführen, vorstellen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to demand",
      "front": "verlangen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to explain",
      "front": "erklären",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to arrive",
      "front": "ankommen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to win",
      "front": "gewinnen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to cut",
      "front": "schneiden",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to put",
      "front": "legen, stellen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to announce",
      "front": "ankündigen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to fit",
      "front": "passen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to sing",
      "front": "singen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to allow",
      "front": "erlauben",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to set sth.",
      "front": "etw. setzen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "studies",
      "front": "Studium",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "teacher",
      "front": "Lehrer",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "note",
      "front": "Notiz",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "mark (BE) / grade (AE)",
      "front": "Note (Schule)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "pen",
      "front": "Stift",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "school",
      "front": "Schule",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "program",
      "front": "Programm",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "education",
      "front": "Bildung",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "section",
      "front": "Bereich",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "course",
      "front": "Kurs",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "library",
      "front": "Bibliothek",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "test",
      "front": "Test",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "application",
      "front": "Anwendung",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "study",
      "front": "Studie",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "example / instance",
      "front": "Beispiel",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "class",
      "front": "Klasse",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "word",
      "front": "Wort",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "knowledge",
      "front": "Wissen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "chapter",
      "front": "Kapitel",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "practice",
      "front": "Praxis",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "institute",
      "front": "Institut",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "idea",
      "front": "Idee",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "professor",
      "front": "Professor",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "presentation",
      "front": "Präsentation",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "preparation",
      "front": "Vorbereitung",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "university",
      "front": "Universität",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "lecture",
      "front": "Vorlesung",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "goal / aim / objective",
      "front": "Ziel",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "meaning",
      "front": "Bedeutung",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "teaching",
      "front": "Lehre",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "training",
      "front": "Training",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "history",
      "front": "Geschichte",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "page",
      "front": "Seite (Buch)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "report",
      "front": "Bericht",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "explanation",
      "front": "Erklärung",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "difficulty",
      "front": "Schwierigkeit",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "document",
      "front": "Dokument",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "yesterday",
      "front": "gestern",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "recently",
      "front": "neulich",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to rent",
      "front": "mieten",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to sell",
      "front": "verkaufen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to place",
      "front": "platzieren",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "love",
      "front": "Liebe",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "part",
      "front": "Teil",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "service",
      "front": "Dienstleistung",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "list",
      "front": "Liste",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "system",
      "front": "System",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "review",
      "front": "Rezension",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "order",
      "front": "Reihenfolge",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "order",
      "front": "Bestellung",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "group",
      "front": "Gruppe",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "way",
      "front": "Weg",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "type",
      "front": "Typ",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "design",
      "front": "Design",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "case",
      "front": "Fall",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "version",
      "front": "Version",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "member",
      "front": "Mitglied",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "control",
      "front": "Kontrolle",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "change",
      "front": "Wechsel",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "call",
      "front": "Anruf",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "account",
      "front": "Konto",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "profile",
      "front": "Profil",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "level / stage",
      "front": "Stufe",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "description",
      "front": "Beschreibung",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "image / picture",
      "front": "Bild",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "content",
      "front": "Inhalt",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "value",
      "front": "Wert",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "category",
      "front": "Kategorie",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "act",
      "front": "Akt",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "equipment",
      "front": "Ausrüstung",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "problem",
      "front": "Problem",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "side",
      "front": "Seite",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "performance",
      "front": "Leistung",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "option",
      "front": "Option",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "activity",
      "front": "Aktivität",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "result",
      "front": "Ergebnis",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "issue",
      "front": "Sachverhalt",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "agreement",
      "front": "Vereinbarung",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "solution",
      "front": "Lösung",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "production",
      "front": "Herstellung",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "protection",
      "front": "Schutz",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "construction",
      "front": "Bau",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "response",
      "front": "Rückmeldung",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "entry",
      "front": "Eintrag",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "effect",
      "front": "Effekt",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "mind",
      "front": "Verstand",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "wish",
      "front": "Wunsch",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "hope",
      "front": "Hoffnung",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "union",
      "front": "Vereinigung",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "opportunity / occasion",
      "front": "Gelegenheit",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "choice",
      "front": "Wahl, Entscheidung",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "selection",
      "front": "Auswahl",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "degree",
      "front": "Grad",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "matter",
      "front": "Angelegenheit",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "voice",
      "front": "Stimme",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "evidence",
      "front": "Beleg",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "role",
      "front": "Rolle",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "purpose",
      "front": "Zweck",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "success",
      "front": "Erfolg",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "introduction",
      "front": "Einführung",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "charge",
      "front": "Gebühr",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "rest / recovery",
      "front": "Erholung",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "subject",
      "front": "Subjekt",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "darkness",
      "front": "Dunkelheit",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "alternative",
      "front": "Alternative",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "kind",
      "front": "Sorte / Art",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "record",
      "front": "Aufnahme",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "edge",
      "front": "Kante",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "bigger than",
      "front": "größer als",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "better",
      "front": "besser",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "best",
      "front": "am besten",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "worse",
      "front": "schlechter",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "worst",
      "front": "am schlechtesten",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to cover",
      "front": "bedecken",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to choose / to select",
      "front": "auswählen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to increase",
      "front": "(sich) vergrößern",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to stay",
      "front": "bleiben",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to build",
      "front": "bauen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to apply",
      "front": "anwenden",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to improve",
      "front": "verbessern",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to repeat",
      "front": "wiederholen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to wake up",
      "front": "aufwachen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to understand",
      "front": "verstehen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to let",
      "front": "lassen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to develop",
      "front": "entwickeln",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to die",
      "front": "sterben",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to accept",
      "front": "akzeptieren",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to avoid / to prevent",
      "front": "vermeiden",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to wait",
      "front": "warten",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to define",
      "front": "definieren",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to reach / to achieve",
      "front": "erreichen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to beat",
      "front": "schlagen, besiegen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to exist",
      "front": "existieren",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to affect",
      "front": "beeinflussen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to lose",
      "front": "verlieren",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to forget",
      "front": "vergessen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to prepare",
      "front": "vorbereiten",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to introduce oneself to so.",
      "front": "sich jm. vorstellen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to shut / to close",
      "front": "schließen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to belong to",
      "front": "gehören zu",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to suffer",
      "front": "leiden",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to recover",
      "front": "sich erholen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to analyze",
      "front": "analysieren",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to establish",
      "front": "gründen, aufbauen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to discover",
      "front": "entdecken",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to earn",
      "front": "verdienen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "respect",
      "front": "Respekt",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "title",
      "front": "Titel",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "benefit",
      "front": "Gewinn",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "situation",
      "front": "Situation",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "religion",
      "front": "Religion",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "effort",
      "front": "Anstrengung",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "attention",
      "front": "Aufmerksamkeit",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "interest",
      "front": "Interesse",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "competition / contest",
      "front": "Wettbewerb",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "life",
      "front": "Leben",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "load",
      "front": "Ladung",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "permission",
      "front": "Erlaubnis",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "faith",
      "front": "Vertrauen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "truth",
      "front": "Wahrheit",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "failure",
      "front": "Misserfolg",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "signal",
      "front": "Signal",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "character",
      "front": "Charakter",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "reality",
      "front": "Realität",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "origin",
      "front": "Ursprung",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "damage",
      "front": "Schaden",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "secret",
      "front": "Geheimnis",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "direction",
      "front": "Richtung",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "lack of",
      "front": "Nichtvorhandensein von",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "scene",
      "front": "Szene",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "behavior",
      "front": "Verhalten",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "signature",
      "front": "Unterschrift",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "attempt",
      "front": "Versuch",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "circle",
      "front": "Kreis",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "exit",
      "front": "Ausgang",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "symbol",
      "front": "Symbol",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "position",
      "front": "Position",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "strength",
      "front": "Stärke",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "experience",
      "front": "Erfahrung",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "shape",
      "front": "Form",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "relation / connection",
      "front": "Verbindung",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "fear",
      "front": "Furcht",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "doubt",
      "front": "Zweifel",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "humor",
      "front": "Humor",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "hate",
      "front": "Hass",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "possibility",
      "front": "Möglichkeit",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "desire",
      "front": "Verlangen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "existence",
      "front": "Existenz",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "pleasure",
      "front": "Vergnügen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "responsibility",
      "front": "Verantwortung",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "surprise",
      "front": "Überraschung",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "tradition",
      "front": "Tradition",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "conversation",
      "front": "Gespräch",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "trend",
      "front": "Trend",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "fault",
      "front": "Schuld",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "favor",
      "front": "Gefallen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "phrase",
      "front": "Redewendung",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "attitude",
      "front": "Einstellung",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "murder",
      "front": "Mord",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "murderer",
      "front": "Mörder",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "mistake / error",
      "front": "Fehler",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "honor",
      "front": "Ehre",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "smile",
      "front": "Lächeln",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "danger",
      "front": "Gefahr",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "joy",
      "front": "Spaß",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "entrance",
      "front": "Eingang",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "shadow",
      "front": "Schatten",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "memory",
      "front": "Gedächtnis",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "flower",
      "front": "Blume",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "tree",
      "front": "Baum",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "grass",
      "front": "Gras",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "sky",
      "front": "Himmel (Natur)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "heaven",
      "front": "Himmel (relig.)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "sea",
      "front": "Meer",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "lake",
      "front": "See",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "moon",
      "front": "Mond",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "sun",
      "front": "Sonne",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "world",
      "front": "Welt",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "rain",
      "front": "Regen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "volcano",
      "front": "Vulkan",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "fire",
      "front": "Feuer",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "air",
      "front": "Luft",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "field",
      "front": "Feld",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "star",
      "front": "Stern",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "weather",
      "front": "Wetter",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "nature",
      "front": "Natur",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "river",
      "front": "Fluss",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "earth",
      "front": "Erde",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "mountain",
      "front": "Berg",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "wood",
      "front": "Holz",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "forest",
      "front": "Wald",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "stone",
      "front": "Stein",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "wind",
      "front": "Wind",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "heat",
      "front": "Hitze",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "rose",
      "front": "Rose",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "planet",
      "front": "Planet",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "up",
      "front": "hoch",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "down",
      "front": "runter",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "climate",
      "front": "Klima",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "universe",
      "front": "Universum",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "leaf",
      "front": "Blatt (Baum)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "landscape",
      "front": "Landschaft",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "smoke",
      "front": "Rauch",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "grain / cereal",
      "front": "Getreide",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "crop / harvest",
      "front": "Ernte",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "gas",
      "front": "Gas",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "material",
      "front": "Material",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "plant",
      "front": "Pflanze",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "light",
      "front": "Licht",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "dust",
      "front": "Staub",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "sand",
      "front": "Sand",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "sports",
      "front": "Sport",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ball",
      "front": "Ball",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "walk",
      "front": "Spaziergang",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "team",
      "front": "Mannschaft",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "player",
      "front": "Spieler",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "step",
      "front": "Schritt",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "path",
      "front": "Pfad",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "goal",
      "front": "Tor (Fußball)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "point",
      "front": "Punkt",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "game",
      "front": "Spiel",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to score a goal",
      "front": "ein Tor erzielen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "score",
      "front": "Spielstand",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "football (BE) / soccer (AE)",
      "front": "Fußball",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "basketball",
      "front": "Basketball",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "tennis",
      "front": "Tennis",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "racket",
      "front": "Schläger",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "volleyball",
      "front": "Volleyball",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to kick",
      "front": "schießen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to jump",
      "front": "springen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "jump",
      "front": "Sprung",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "coach",
      "front": "Trainer",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "exercise",
      "front": "Übung",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "match",
      "front": "Match",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "marathon",
      "front": "Marathon",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "gym",
      "front": "Sporthalle",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "championship",
      "front": "Meisterschaft",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "athlete",
      "front": "Athlet",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "swimming",
      "front": "Schwimmen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "violin",
      "front": "Geige",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "flute",
      "front": "Flöte",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "music",
      "front": "Musik",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "camera",
      "front": "Kamera",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "photo",
      "front": "Foto",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "film (BE) / movie (AE)",
      "front": "Film",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "art",
      "front": "Kunst",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "style",
      "front": "Stil",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "sound",
      "front": "Geräusch",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "figure",
      "front": "Figur",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "song",
      "front": "Lied",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "photography",
      "front": "Fotografie",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "dance",
      "front": "Tanz",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "instrument",
      "front": "Instrument",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "literature",
      "front": "Literatur",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "fashion",
      "front": "Mode",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "theater",
      "front": "Theater",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "poetry",
      "front": "Poesie",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "concert",
      "front": "Konzert",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "opening",
      "front": "Eröffnung",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "painting",
      "front": "Gemälde",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to paint",
      "front": "malen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "audience",
      "front": "Publikum",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "collection",
      "front": "Sammlung",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "band",
      "front": "Band",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "musical",
      "front": "Musical",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "search",
      "front": "Suche",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "information",
      "front": "Information",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "comment",
      "front": "Kommentar",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "network",
      "front": "Netzwerk",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "press",
      "front": "Presse",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "text",
      "front": "Text",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "channel",
      "front": "Kanal",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "communication",
      "front": "Kommunikation",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "news",
      "front": "Nachrichten",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "message",
      "front": "Nachricht",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "Internet",
      "front": "Internet",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "language",
      "front": "Sprache",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "stamp",
      "front": "Briefmarke",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "access",
      "front": "Zugang",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "journalist",
      "front": "Journalist",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "a story",
      "front": "eine Geschichte",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "postcard",
      "front": "Postkarte",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "sick / ill",
      "front": "krank",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "hand",
      "front": "Hand",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "eye",
      "front": "Auge",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "health",
      "front": "Gesundheit",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "care",
      "front": "Pflege",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "body",
      "front": "Körper",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "head",
      "front": "Kopf",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "help",
      "front": "Hilfe",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "emergency",
      "front": "Notfall",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "treatment",
      "front": "Behandlung",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "heart",
      "front": "Herz",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "face",
      "front": "Gesicht",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "cancer",
      "front": "Krebs (Krankheit)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "medicine",
      "front": "Medizin",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ambulance",
      "front": "Krankenwagen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "blood",
      "front": "Blut",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "disease / illness",
      "front": "Krankheit",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "hair",
      "front": "Haar",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "patient",
      "front": "Patient",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "patience",
      "front": "Geduld",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "patient",
      "front": "geduldig",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "hospital",
      "front": "Krankenhaus",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "operation",
      "front": "Operation",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "skin",
      "front": "Haut",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "foot",
      "front": "Fuß",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "diet",
      "front": "Diät",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "sight / view",
      "front": "Sicht",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "pain",
      "front": "Schmerz",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "drug",
      "front": "Droge",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "virus",
      "front": "Virus",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "brain",
      "front": "Gehirn",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "arm",
      "front": "Arm",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "leg",
      "front": "Bein",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "mouth",
      "front": "Mund",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "dream",
      "front": "Traum",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "accident",
      "front": "Unfall",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "neck",
      "front": "Hals",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "finger",
      "front": "Finger",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "ear",
      "front": "Ohr",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "chest",
      "front": "Brust",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "tooth",
      "front": "Zahn",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "teeth",
      "front": "Zähne",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "tongue",
      "front": "Zunge",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "nose",
      "front": "Nase",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "lip",
      "front": "Lippe",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "back",
      "front": "Rücken",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "condition",
      "front": "Zustand",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "condition",
      "front": "Bedingung",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "appointment",
      "front": "Termin",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "nurse",
      "front": "Krankenschwester",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "security / safety",
      "front": "Sicherheit",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "law",
      "front": "Gesetz",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "government",
      "front": "Regierung",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "tax",
      "front": "Steuer",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "court",
      "front": "Gericht",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "war",
      "front": "Krieg",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "president",
      "front": "Präsident",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "national",
      "front": "national",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "nation",
      "front": "Nation",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "society",
      "front": "Gesellschaft",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "advice",
      "front": "Rat",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "investment",
      "front": "Investition",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to vote",
      "front": "wählen (polit.)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "vote",
      "front": "Wählerstimme",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "strategy",
      "front": "Strategie",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "opinion",
      "front": "Meinung",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "dept",
      "front": "Schulden",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "progress",
      "front": "Fortschritt",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "peace",
      "front": "Frieden",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "economy",
      "front": "Wirtschaft",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "army",
      "front": "Armee",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "demand",
      "front": "Nachfrage",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "crime",
      "front": "Kriminalität",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "leader",
      "front": "Führer",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "freedom",
      "front": "Freiheit",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "argument",
      "front": "Streit",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "campaign",
      "front": "Kampagne",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "congress",
      "front": "Kongress",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "election",
      "front": "Wahl (polit.)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "queen",
      "front": "Königin",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "speech",
      "front": "Rede",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "violence",
      "front": "Gewalt",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "conflict",
      "front": "Konflikt",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "navy",
      "front": "Marine",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "candidate",
      "front": "Kandidat",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "threat",
      "front": "Bedrohung",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "governor",
      "front": "Gouverneur",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "senator",
      "front": "Senator",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "crisis",
      "front": "Krise",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "parliament",
      "front": "Parlament",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "strike",
      "front": "Streik",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "mayor",
      "front": "Bürgermeister",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "wealth",
      "front": "Reichtum, Wohlstand",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to blame",
      "front": "beschuldigen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "plan",
      "front": "Plan",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "decision",
      "front": "Entscheidung",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "king",
      "front": "König",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "cause",
      "front": "Ursache",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "weapon",
      "front": "Waffe",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to arrest",
      "front": "verhaften",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "prince",
      "front": "Prinz",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "research",
      "front": "Forschung",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "line",
      "front": "Linie",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "detail",
      "front": "Detail",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "technology",
      "front": "Technologie",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "project",
      "front": "Projekt",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "size",
      "front": "Größe",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "article",
      "front": "Artikel",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "science",
      "front": "Wissenschaft",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "analysis",
      "front": "Analyse",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "energy",
      "front": "Energie",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "edition",
      "front": "Edition",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "unit",
      "front": "Einheit",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "weight",
      "front": "Gewicht",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "method",
      "front": "Methode",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "speed / velocity",
      "front": "Geschwindigkeit",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "volume",
      "front": "Volumen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "length",
      "front": "Länge",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "sample",
      "front": "Stichprobe",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "distance",
      "front": "Entfernung",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "publication",
      "front": "Veröffentlichung",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "theory",
      "front": "Theorie",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "surface",
      "front": "Oberfläche",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "definition",
      "front": "Definition",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "scale",
      "front": "Skala",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "temperature",
      "front": "Temperatur",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "technique",
      "front": "Technik",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "mass",
      "front": "Masse",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "limit",
      "front": "Grenze (techn.)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "quantity",
      "front": "Menge",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "task",
      "front": "Aufgabe",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "laboratory",
      "front": "Labor",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "depth",
      "front": "Tiefe",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "height",
      "front": "Höhe",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "physics",
      "front": "Physik",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "philosophy",
      "front": "Philosophie",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "measure",
      "front": "Maß",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "concept",
      "front": "Konzept",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "chemistry",
      "front": "Chemue",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "discovery",
      "front": "Entdeckung",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "formula",
      "front": "Formel",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "investigation / examination",
      "front": "Untersuchung",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "scientist",
      "front": "Wissenschaftler",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "geography",
      "front": "Geographie",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "electric",
      "front": "elektisch",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "electricity",
      "front": "Elektrizität",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "cycle",
      "front": "Kreislauf",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "conclusion",
      "front": "Schlussfolgerung",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "reason",
      "front": "Grund",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "decrease",
      "front": "Abnahme",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "alcohol",
      "front": "Alkohol",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "money",
      "front": "Geld",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "two dollars",
      "front": "zwei Dollar",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "business",
      "front": "Geschäft",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "product",
      "front": "Produkt",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "board",
      "front": "Vorstand",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "insurance",
      "front": "Versicherung",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "sale",
      "front": "Verkauf",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "credit card",
      "front": "Kreditkarte",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "industry",
      "front": "Industrie",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "offer",
      "front": "Angebot",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "gold",
      "front": "Gold",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "silver",
      "front": "Silber",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "trade",
      "front": "Handel",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "risk",
      "front": "Risiko",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "brand",
      "front": "Marke",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "contract",
      "front": "Vertrag",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "deal",
      "front": "Geschäft, Abmachung",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "budget",
      "front": "Etat",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "agent",
      "front": "Vertreter",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "worth",
      "front": "wert",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "currency",
      "front": "Währung",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "advertisement",
      "front": "Werbung",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "promotion",
      "front": "Beförderung",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "prize / award",
      "front": "Preis (Wettbewerb)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "price",
      "front": "Preis (einer Ware)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "firm",
      "front": "Firma",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "to advert",
      "front": "werben",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "costs",
      "front": "Kosten",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "organization",
      "front": "Organisation",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "interview",
      "front": "Interview",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "job interview",
      "front": "Vorstellungsgespräch",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "meeting",
      "front": "Besprechung",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "company",
      "front": "Unternehmen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "global",
      "front": "global",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "action",
      "front": "Aktion",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "start",
      "front": "Start",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "delivery",
      "front": "Lieferung",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "discussion",
      "front": "Diskussion",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "death",
      "front": "Tod",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "traffic",
      "front": "Verkehr",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "attack",
      "front": "Angriff",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "battle",
      "front": "Schlacht",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "noise",
      "front": "Lärm",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "can / may",
      "front": "kann / darf",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "must",
      "front": "muss",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "shall",
      "front": "soll",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "must not",
      "front": "darf nicht",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "should",
      "front": "sollte",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "would",
      "front": "würde",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "could",
      "front": "könnte",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "power / force",
      "front": "Kraft",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "quality",
      "front": "Qualität",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "look",
      "front": "Blick",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "looks",
      "front": "Aussehen",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "beauty",
      "front": "Schönheit",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "difference",
      "front": "Unterschied",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "identity",
      "front": "Identität",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "impression",
      "front": "Eindruck",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "expression",
      "front": "Ausdruck",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "importance",
      "front": "Wichtigkeit",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "luck",
      "front": "Glück (Zufall)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "happiness",
      "front": "Glück (Gefühl)",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "personality",
      "front": "Persönlichkeit",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "back": "advantage",
      "front": "Vorteil",
      "level": 2
    }
  ],
  "file": "Duolingo_German",
  "back": "en",
  "description": "Learning German for English speakers"
}